entelo.com 2019-11-13

# Cookie Policy | Entelo

**Notice: We updated our Privacy Policy in Feb 2019.**

To view our archived privacy policies, please visit:

_Last updated: February 14, 2019_

_What changed: We described some aspects of our commitment to the Privacy Shield framework in more detail. We explained that personal data collected by Entelo now may include telephone numbers of job candidates based in the United States._

Entelo, Inc. is a web-based software solution that allows recruiting professionals to recruit faster, smarter and better by using predictive algorithms and data-backed insights. We gather information about our Users, those that interact with our Website, products and Services, and about  job candidate profiles, to provide a better, more focused experience for you.

We at Entelo know you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Our Privacy Notice will help you understand what information we collect and receive at Entelo, how Entelo uses it, and what choices you have.For this Privacy Notice, the words “our,” “us,” “we,” and “Entelo” refer to Entelo, Inc., and our affiliates, if any, (which includes any person or entity that controls us, is controlled by us, or is under common control with us, such as our subsidiary (if applicable), parent company (if applicable), or our employees). This Privacy Notice does not cover the practices of companies we don’t own or control, or people that we don’t manage. This Privacy Notice is not intended to place any limits on what we do with data that is anonymized or de-identified so it is no longer associated with an identifiable individual.

This Privacy Notice is separated into six sections:

  1. Our Website. This section describes the type of data collected from our publicly-accessible Website.
  2. Our Marketing Activities. This section describes that from time to time, Entelo will reach out to you in a variety of ways to tell you about products, Services and other information we believe is relevant to you.
  3. Entelo Services for Customers. This section describes the type of data collected from our software-as-a-service applications and other products and Services (collectively the “Services”) that we provide to customers who have purchased Services (“Customer”), including each person who is an authorized user under that Customer’s account (“User”). Every User must have a unique account and password to use the Services.
  4. Job Candidates. This section outlines how we collect data about potential job candidates. Please note that we may collect information about you even if you do not have a User account and never visit our Website.
  5. This section describes how we use cookies, beacons and other online tracking technologies in greater detail.
  6. This section outlines general concepts that apply to the types of data we collect from all types of persons. It also explains how we communicate changes to this , and how you may contact us regarding any questions or issues with respect to anything contained within this Privacy Notice.

**By using or accessing the Website or Entelo’s Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Notice, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways.**

**SECTION I: ENTELO WEBSITE**

Below is a description of what data we gather from you as a visitor to our various publicly accessible websites, which include  _[https://entelo.com](https://entelo.com/)_ , _[blog.entelo.com](https://blog.entelo.com/)_ and other websites where this Privacy Notice is posted. For ease, we will call all these publicly accessible websites collectively the “Website” for short. The Entelo Website does not include our account portal, or other access to our Services that you get when you sign up for an account with Entelo. Information about data collected through the account portal (and other data collected as a consequence of having an account) is located in Section III “Services” below.

In this section, “you” may refer to an individual, company or other entity visiting the Entelo Website.

  1. **What data we collect and how we collect it**
  2. **Information You Provide to Us**

**When you request a demo or request to be contacted.** We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us. For example, to request a demo of the Services you must provide your: first name, last name, company name, phone number, email address and company size.

**When you Comment on our Blog.   **If you want to comment on our blog posts at blog.entelo.com you first must register by providing your: first and last name and email address. You also may provide an optional website URL.

**When You Use the Services.** Please refer to the section **“** _Services and Your Customer Account Information.”_

  2. **Information We Collect Automatically**

When you visit the Entelo Website, we and our service providers acting on our behalf automatically collect certain data using tracking technologies like cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies. This information includes: the time of your visit, pages visited, referring site, search engine and keywords used to reach our Website, information about your device and browser, your location by city and country, your IP address, your username and real name, and your email address.

Please see Section V for more information about cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies.

  1. **How we use this data**

We may use this data to communicate with you if you’ve provided us the means to do so. For example, if you’ve given us your email address, we may send you promotional emails about Entelo, or email you about your use of the Website. Also, we track when you open and click an email from us. This confirmation helps us make our communications with you more interesting and improve our Services. If you do not want to receive communications from us, please indicate your preference by opting out via the links provided in the emails.

When you comment on our blog posts we use your first and last name to identify you as the commenter alongside your blog comment. We use your email and website information to email you with marketing offers and resources, newsletters and other company updates. If you opt in, we also use your email to send you follow up comments for that blog post. We may take down blog comments which we deem inappropriate.

We use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies to help us better understand visitor and user behavior.

  1. **How we share this data**

Unless you explicitly give us instructions not to share or collect data, we will share data we collect from you with third parties as described at Section VI.B (How we share your data in general). We might share data collected from you from the Entelo Website with a third party if that data has been anonymized, pseudonymised or aggregated in a way that does not directly identify you.

We also may share data collected from you with a third party we have partnered with for the purpose of inviting you to our company programs (for example webinars, field events, or other offers).

**SECTION II: MARKETING ACTIVITIES**

We market our company, products and Services in a variety of methods. Below is a description of what data we gather from you, and how we use data given to us, as part of these marketing activities.

In this section, “you” may refer to a variety of people, including:

  * Individuals or entities who have no relationship with Entelo, who may be interested in becoming Entelo Customers. Entelo has acquired data about them through a third party. (“Leads”)
  * Individuals or entities who already have contacted Entelo or otherwise inquired about Entelo’s products or Services who may be interested in becoming Entelo Customers. (“Prospects”)
  * Individuals or entities who use currently use Entelo’s products and Services (“Customers”)

If there are special terms and considerations, we will address the individual group by the capitalized term (Lead, Prospect or Customer). Where terms apply to all groups, we will address the group as “you.”

  1. **What data we collect and how we collect it**
  2. **You may give us data directly.**

If you elect to interact with Entelo, we will collect the information you provide to us in doing so.

Prospects and Customers may provide Entelo directly with data through a variety of methods, for example: during a marketing event that Entelo hosts, through email, or as part of an online webinar. We collect and store the information you provide. Occasionally, we may send you future communications, and as part of these future communications we may collect more data that you directly provide.

  2. **We may acquire information about you through a third party.**

Entelo may engage third parties, who provide us with contact information for Leads. When acquiring information from third parties, Entelo will obtain contractual commitments from the third parties that the Lead information was acquired lawfully.

  1. **What we do with this data**

Generally, we use all the data described in this Section II that you provide to us or that we collect to provide you marketing and promotional information about our products and Services. Communications will contain instructions on how you can opt-out of receiving future communications. You also may contact Entelo directly about its marketing activities at privacy@entelo.com.

  1. **How we share this data**

_Third-Party Advertising Partners and Other Service Providers_. We use third-party advertising networks to serve advertisements (for example, sidebar ads, banners or search ads) about our products to you on our behalf when you visit other websites within that advertising network. We may use third-party service providers to serve customized content to you on our Website. In order to enable the advertising described in this paragraph Entelo may provide your data to the third party service provider, but we only disclose the information that the service provider requires to perform its requested function.  We do not authorize the service provider to retain, share, store, or use personal information provided by us for any other purpose.

See Section VI.B (How we share your data generally).

**SECTION III: ENTELO SERVICE**

This Section contains a description of data we collect or process through our Services (not our Website) and that relates to a Customer, a User or a potential job candidate.

Where terms in this Section III apply to all three groups (Customer, User and job candidate), we will address the group as “you.”

  1. **What data we collect and how we collect it**
  2. **Customers and Users provide data directly to the Services or Entelo.**

_User account information_. In order to use the Services, the Customer must provide an email address, account user name and account password for each User to the Services.

_Candidate attributes._ Through the use of the Search and Envoy Services, the Customer and its Users can provide details of the position which they want to fill. Their search criteria can be based on geography, skills, job titles, company name or industry of the prospective candidates. We therefore use and process only the search criteria that our Customers provide to us.

_Job openings and qualifications_. In addition, through the Envoy Services, a Customer and its Users can provide descriptions of the positions that are open and descriptions of the qualifications of the desired job candidate for each open position. Customers and Users also can provide comments on each of their job openings and job candidates. This information is collected, used and shared only between Customer and its Users within the Services.

_Information provided by telephone or email_. Customer and Users also may provide data to Entelo by telephone or email, to request informational or technical support for the Services or to provide feedback on the Services. Entelo may ask the Customer or User for additional personally identifiable information, such as first and last name, account email and password.

  2. **We collect information about Job Candidates.**

See Section IV “Job Candidates.”

  3. **Data Collected Automatically.**

Certain Customers integrate their human resources applicant tracking system (“ATS”) software with the Services. When this happens, Entelo receives only  information about the job candidate that has been imported by Customer into its ATS.  This is information that a Customer has collected and wishes to share with Entelo. Entelo  uses this information within the Services to improve the workflow for that Customer and does not otherwise share this information.

Additionally, when Customers and Users use the Services Entelo and its service providers acting on its behalf automatically collect certain data using tracking technologies like cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies. See Section V below for more information.

  4. **We may acquire anonymized, aggregated data that relates to You.**

Entelo has developed proprietary algorithms that monitor all transactions that occur within the Services. The purpose of these algorithms is to identify patterns of behavior, either unique to a User or to defined categories of people, which may enhance a User’s use of the Services. Any data created or identified within an algorithm does not identify the activity of an individual User or job candidate. For example, we continuously improve our algorithms for trying to recognize the semantic meaning behind various attributes in a search query.

  1. **What we do with this data**

Entelo uses the support services information and feedback described at Section III.A(1) in order to respond effectively to support requests, to fully understand feedback, to better understand how Customers and Users use the Services and to improve or expand the Services.

Generally, we use all the data that you provide to us or that we collect from you to provide the Services to you, to enable you to access and use the Services, to deliver your communications to their intended destination, and to analyze your use of the Services, to improve, enhance and expand our products and Services, and to detect fraudulent or unlawful activity in connection with your Entelo account.

  1. **How we share this data**

See Section VI.B (How we share your data generally).

_External Services_. The Services allow you to send or receive communications to end user contacts through email communications. If you send communications through the Services, Entelo will deliver those communications to third party delivery networks in order for the end user contact to share and receive those communications. We call these third party delivery networks “External Services.” Examples of External Services include Sendgrid (for email delivery). How these External Services handle your communications once that information is handed off to the External Service network is determined by their own policies.

_Aggregated or de-identified data_. We might also share data collected from you from the Services with a third party if that data has been de-identified or aggregated in a way that does not directly identify you.

**SECTION IV: JOB CANDIDATES**

  1. **What data we collect and how we collect it**

If you work and are a college graduate, then we may collect information about you from publicly-available websites or from third party vendors who have the license to provide such information to us. This information is limited to your contact information and information regarding your professional qualifications. We do not collect sensitive information, such as data related to your health or political orientation.

More specifically, the information that we collect about you will include personally identifiable and other information such as name, address, education, qualifications, work history, work title, email address, telephone number if you are a  U.S. resident and achievements. We also collect information related to your profession you have provided to your social media profiles such as GitHub, Facebook, and Twitter, but only if the profile was available to the public when it was first indexed by Internet search engines.

In order to better understand job candidates and provide a better experience for our Customers, Entelo may create job candidate “profiles” within the Services for some job candidates. For example, the Services may curate some job candidate profiles for Customers by profiling the candidate within the Services as “likely to move” to a new job soon.

You have the opportunity to claim information Entelo collects that relates to you and correct the information or remove the information from our Services, as described in Section VI of this Privacy Notice. However we cannot guarantee that we will not later collect other information that pertains to you from publicly available websites or third party vendors.

  1. **What we do with this data**

We may use this information to create a candidate profile, or append it to an existing candidate profile. We provide some candidate profiles to Customers who subscribe to the Services, depending on the candidate profile requirements established by each Customer. We do this for the purpose of finding candidates for open job positions with our Customers.

  1. **How we share your data**

We may share your data with our Customers and Users who are typically recruiters or recruiting managers or hiring managers.  In some case, we may share aggregated, anonymized or non-anonymized data with our Customers for purposes other than recruiting (for example, to understand  job candidate diversity in different geographic regions).

**SECTION V: COOKIES**

When you visit the Entelo Website or use the Services, or both, we and our third party service providers acting on our behalf automatically collect certain data using tracking technologies like cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies.

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

These technologies are used to help us better understand user behavior and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of our Entelo Website and Services. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information.

We use cookies to record current session information. We also use third party cookies (for example Google Analytics) to provide anonymized and aggregated information on Website usage statistics and patterns.

All modern Internet browsers allow you to control your cookie settings. These settings are usually accessed in the ‘Options’ or ‘Preferences’ section of your browser. On your mobile device, go to Settings, then go to the specific web-browser, and then to the Cookies section. Please note that certain features of the Website will not be available once cookies are disabled. For further information about cookies and how to manage them, please visit  _[www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)_.

Entelo uses web beacons with cookies or separately to compile information about your engagement with us. Web beacons are clear electronic images that can recognize certain types of information on your computer, such as cookies, when you view a particular website tied to the web beacon, and a description of a website tied to the web beacon.

Here is a basic description and overview of the type of cookies Entelo uses:

**Cookie Type** | **Description** | **Management Setting**  
---|---|---  
_Required Cookies_ | Required cookies make it possible for you to access the Services, navigate within the Services, and access information related to your account. 

Each time you log into the Services, a cookie containing an encrypted, unique identifier that is tied to your account is placed on your browser. These cookies allow Entelo to uniquely identify you when you are logged into the Services and to process your requests.

| Required cookies are necessary to operate the account portal, so you can’t opt out of them.  
_Functionality Cookies_ | Functionality cookies allow the Entelo Website and Services to remember information you have entered or preferences you select, and provide enhanced, more personal features. These cookies allow you to optimize your use of the Services after logging in. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to the portions of your account that you can customize. | You can use your browser settings to opt out of functionality cookies. For more information on how to do that, click  _[here](http://www.aboutcookies.org/)_. Note that opting out may affect the functionality of our Website or Services for you.  
_Performance Cookies_ | These cookies collect data about how visitors use the Entelo Website or Services. This includes data like which pages visitors go to the most. These cookies don’t collect information that individually identifies visitors. The data these cookies collect is aggregated and intended to be anonymous and used to improve how the site functions and performs. |    
_Third party service providers that currently place performance cookies within the Services or Entelo Website include:_  
  | Google Analytics: We use Google Analytics to help analyze page statistics and user behavior to the Entelo Website and Services. | For information on how to opt-out of tracking technologies from Google Analytics,  _[click here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=None)_.  
  | Optimizely: We use Optimizely to optimize page content on the Entelo Website and Services. | For information on how to opt-out of tracking technologies from Optimizely, click  _[here](https://www.optimizely.com/opt_out/)_.  
  | New Relic Systems: We use New Relic to help analyze Website page performance | For information on New Relic’s cookie policy, click  _[here](https://docs.newrelic.com/docs/browser/new-relic-browser/page-load-timing-resources/new-relic-cookies)_.  
  | AppCues: We use AppCues to help analyze user behavior within the Services. | For information on Appcues’ Privacy Notice, click  _[here](https://www.appcues.com/privacy)_.  
  | Mixpanel: We use Mixpanel to help analyze user behavior within the Services. | For information on Mixpanel’s Privacy Notice, click  _[here](https://www.appcues.com/privacy)_.  
_Advertising Cookies_ | Entelo may have third party service providers track and analyze usage and volume statistical information from those who visit the Entelo Website and Services. Entelo sometimes uses cookies placed by its third party service providers to track the performance of our advertisements. For example, these cookies remember which browsers have visited the Entelo Websites or the Services. This data given to the third party service providers does not include information that identifies you specifically, but this data may be re-associated with information that identifies you specifically after Entelo receives it. | To learn more about how to opt out of targeting and advertising cookies, you can go to the  _[Your Online Choices page](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices)_ , the  _[Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)_  page, and the  _[Digital Advertising Alliance’s Consumer Choice](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)_ page. These opt-out tools are provided by third parties, not Entelo. We do not control or operate these tools or the choices that advertisers and others provide through these tools.  
  
**Section VI: GENERAL**

  1. **How we secure your data**

Entelo take security very seriously.

We use appropriate security measures to protect the security of your data both online and offline. These measures vary based on the sensitivity of the information that we collect, process and store and the current state of technology. Entelo has completed SOC2 Type 2 compliance. For more information regarding our security measures please visit _[here](https://www.entelo.com/products/security/)_. Please note, though, that no website or Internet transmission is completely secure, so while we strive to protect your data, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss or a data breach will never occur.

  1. **How we share your data in general**

We describe some specific ways that we share some of your data in the Sections above. However, in general, unless you give us your permission, we won’t share your data with third parties, except as described here.

  * **Business transfers**. We may choose to buy or sell assets from time to time. We may share Customer information in connection with the evaluation of such transactions. We may transfer Customer information if we enter into such transactions. Also, if we (or our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, personal information could be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.
  * **Third-party service providers or consultants**. We may share data collected from you through the Services with third-party service providers or consultants who need access to the data to perform their work on Entelo’s behalf, such as our cloud hosting service provider. These third party service providers are limited to only accessing or using this data to provide services to us and must provide reasonable assurances that they will appropriately safeguard the data.
  * **To Protect Entelo and Others.  **We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we reasonably believe is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply this Privacy Notice, our Subscription Agreement with a Customer, and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Entelo, our employees, our Users, or others. If Entelo is required by law to disclose any of your data that directly identifies you, then we will use reasonable efforts to provide you with notice of that disclosure requirement, unless we are prohibited from doing so by statute, subpoena or court or administrative order. Further, we object to requests that we do not believe were issued properly.

  1. **Offline Information**

As you might expect, we usually collect or receive information through our Website.  But we also may collect information offline, and it’s important to us that we preserve the privacy of your personal information both online and off.  For example, if you call us with a support question, we may ask for your location. There are other ways we could learn of personal information offline, but this Privacy Notice doesn’t try to predict all those methods.  We just want you to know that we try to treat offline information collection, uses, and disclosures consistently with our online privacy practices.

  1. **Privacy Shield Framework; International Operations and Transfers Out of the EEA**

Entelo’s own data centers are located in the United States and by using our Services, interacting with our Website, or otherwise providing your personal data to us, your personal data will be transferred to and processed in the United States except as stated below in this Section.

Entelo complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield framework (“Privacy Shield”) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from data subjects who reside in the EU, and which has been adopted by the EEA. Entelo has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of notice, choice, accountability for onward transfer, security, data integrity and purpose limitation, access, and recourse, enforcement and liability. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view Entelo’s certification, please visit the Privacy Shield website at https://[www.privacyshield.gov](http://www.privacyshield.gov/)/. With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Entelo is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the United States Federal Trade Commission.

In some cases, Entelo may share your personal data with its subprocessors, to the extent permitted by applicable law. Each of these subprocessors are limited to accessing or using this data to provide our hosted services only and must provide reasonable assurances that they will appropriately safeguard any customer data provided by Entelo. Each of these subprocessors using customer data complies with the Privacy Shield and  processes this data in the United States only, with the exception of SendGrid. SendGrid provides email optimization services for some customers of Entelo. SendGrid  processes personal data in regions it determines, currently the United States, England, Japan and India.

We have implemented safeguards to ensure an adequate level of data protection where your personal data is transferred to countries outside the EEA, such as standard contractual clauses for the transfer of personal data as approved by the European Commission (Art. 46 GDPR).

In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EEA individuals received pursuant to the Privacy Shield, Entelo is potentially liable.

  1. **Information from Children**

We do not knowingly collect any personal information directly from children under the age of 16. If we discover we have received any personal information from a child under the age of 16 in violation of this Notice, we will take reasonable steps to delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe we have any information from or about anyone under the age of 16, please contact us at [privacy@entelo.com](mailto:privacy@entelo.com).

  1. **How we treat Do-Not-Track Signals**

Your browser may offer you a “Do Not Track” option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services (including behavioral advertising services) that you do not wish such operators to track certain of your online activities over time and across different websites. Our Website does not recognize or respond to Do Not Track requests because there is no consistent industry standard for compliance. To learn more about Do Not Track please visit <http://www.allaboutdnt.org/>.

  1. **Communication**
  2. **How we tell you about changes to our privacy practices**

We may periodically update this Notice. We will notify you about material changes (for example material changes to the use of your personal information) in this Privacy Notice by placing a prominent notice on our Website. We will comply with applicable law with respect to any changes we make to this Privacy Notice.

  2. **How to make choices about your data**

_Website_. How you make choices about cookies and other tracking technologies depends on the type of cookie or tracking technology being used. For details on how to manage your preferences for cookies and tracking technologies within your web browser, please re-read Section V of this Privacy Notice.

_Marketing Activities_. If you are receiving promotional emails from us, you can choose to stop receiving them by following the unsubscribe/opt-out instructions in those emails. You can also opt-out by contacting privacy@entelo.com.

_Our Services_. To request access to, deletion of, or changes to data we’ve collected from you via the Services, email us at [privacy@entelo.com](mailto:privacy@entelo.com). Please note that even if you request that we delete data we’ve collected from you, we may still retain data collected from you in an aggregated or anonymized form that does not identify you. We also will not delete your data if we are legally required to maintain it.

_Job Candidates_. To request access to, deletion of, or changes to data we’ve collected about you as a job candidate that may be provided to our Customers, email us at _[privacy@entelo.com](mailto:privacy@entelo.com)_. However we cannot guarantee that we will not later collect other information that pertains to you as a job candidate from publicly available websites or third party vendors. Please note that even if you request that we delete data we’ve collected about you, we may still retain data collected from you in an aggregated or anonymized form that does not identify you. We also will not delete your data if we are legally required to maintain it.

  3. **How to resolve disputes relating to our privacy practices**

Except for residents of the European Union, if you have a dispute with us relating to our privacy practices, please email us at _privacy@entelo.com_. Most disputes can be resolved that way. If you are a Customer or a User and we can’t resolve our dispute that way, then please consult your subscription services agreement with Entelo.

For European residents, we have chosen the EU Data Protection Authorities (EU DPAs) to serve as an independent recourse mechanism for dispute resolution arising from collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from EU member countries to the United States.  If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Notice, please contact us first at  _[privacy@entelo.com](mailto:privacy@entelo.com)_. If contacting us does not resolve your complaint, you may file a complaint, free of charge, with the relevant EU DPA. Entelo will cooperate with the United States Federal Trade Commissions and any DPAs in the investigation and resolution of complaints that cannot be resolved between Entelo and the complainant that are brought to a relevant DPA.

Further, as described at https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint, you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolutions procedures have been exhausted. **4.   California residents  **

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California residents are entitled to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to request this information then please submit a written request to privacy@entelo.com.

  5. **Data Retention and Deletion**

For Website visitors and job candidates, Entelo will retain your information as long as reasonably useful for commercial purposes. To request deletion of your data email us at privacy@entelo.com.

For Entelo Customers, we will retain your account information for as long as your account is active or as reasonably useful for commercial purposes. If you want Entelo to delete portions of your data used to provide you Services, then please email us at support@entelo.com. We process Customer requests for data deletion within ten (10) business days of receipt of the request.

If you are an Entelo Customer and no longer want Entelo to use your data to provide you Services, you may close your account.  If you close your account then you no longer will be able to use the Services. To delete your account entirely, please email us at support@entelo.com.

You should not expect that all of your information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your request.  Some information may remain in our records after we delete your account. Entelo will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

  6. **Changes to this Notice**

We are constantly trying to improve our Website and the Services, so this Privacy Notice may need to change. If we change the Privacy Notice then we will notify you here in this Privacy Notice. If you continue to use the Website or Services, or both, after those changes are in effect then you agree to the revised notice.

  7. **How to contact us**

Any questions about this Privacy Notice or requests for access to or deletion or rectification of data should be addressed

  * by email to: _[privacy@entelo.com](mailto:privacy@entelo.com)_ or
  * by mail to: Entelo, Attn: Legal, 123 Mission Street, 24th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94105, USA.

We prefer email.
